double8tickets.com 2012-12-18

# tickets, Concert Tickets, Double8tickets.com

**Thank you!**  
Thank you for using Double8Tickets.com, London's favourite ticket broker. Please check your tickets immediately on receipt, as queries should be dealt with within 48 hours. 

**About us**  
We are the UK's leading established ticket broker and have been trading from Charing Cross Road, London WC2 for over 15 years. We specialise in obtaining exclusive 'first 10 rows' and 'impossible to get' tickets for sold out shows, concerts and sporting events. Please not that you are often purchasing tickets above face value. This price includes service charges reflecting our costs and efforts in obtaining your premium seats. Please be aware that the ticket market is a very volatile and fluctuating market, and therefore ticket prices may vary wildly at different points in time. 

Please also note, although we specialise in the 'First 10 rows' it does not mean all our tickets are in the 'First 10 rows'. We have different options to cater for different budgets. The option for 'First 10 rows' is always clearly shown. 'Block A' does not mean 'First 10 rows', 'Block B' does not mean 'First 10 rows'. Block behind 'VIP' does not mean 'First 10 rows' and 'General reserved' seats **definitely** does not mean 'First 10 rows'. If you are not sure about what option you are buying do not use this site, or telephone for clarification.

**All sales are final**  
Once an order is placed and paid for, it cannot be cancelled or refunded. Upon request we will try to resell unwanted tickets and, if successful, refund your money less a 25% handling fee. We are not responsible for lost or stolen tickets, and we regret that **WE CANNOT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES ISSUE DUPLICATE TICKETS. PLEASE TREAT YOUR TICKETS LIKE CASH!**

The client should note that the right to cancel or "cooling off period" provided by the Consumer Protection (Distance Selling) Regulations 2000 does not apply to the sale of event tickets. All sales are final.

**In the event of cancellation/rescheduling**  
If an event is cancelled by the artist or promoter, we will refund the **face value** of the ticket only. If an event is rescheduled by the artist or promoter and you cannot attend we will refund the **face value** of the tickets only. We do not have any control over these events. We will not be liable for costs of travel fares, hotels, or any other expenses that may be incurred if a concert is cancelled/rescheduled. It is your responsibility to ensure the concert is going ahead before travelling. We will do our best to inform you if the date has been changed but we do not accept liability if we are unable to contact you. We strongly advise that you check before making arrangements. 

**Delivery of tickets**  
We will endeavour to deliver your tickets as soon as possible. Usually, tickets will be despatched within 7 days from the time of booking. In some cases, due to the nature of the business, tickets do not arrive with us until shortly before the concert date. This is especially common where the tickets in question are general admission (standing) tickets, or specially printed souvenir tickets. These tickets are held back by the promoter as a prevention measure against loss of tickets, fraud or counterfeiting of the tickets. In extreme circumstances, tickets do not arrive with us until the date of the show. If the tickets arrive with us too late to be posted, we will arrange for you to collect your tickets either from our London shop or from a representative at the venue.

**Other notes**  
If your first choice of tickets is not available we reserve the right to upgrade your seats at no extra cost, downgrade with a partial refund or offer you a ticket for the same venue/artist on a different date. If we are unable to offer you any of these alternatives we will cancel your order with a **Golden refund**. A **Golden refund** entitles you to a full refund of the price you paid for the tickets, plus an additional 25% on top, as our way of saying "sorry we let you down". We will also give you a free upgrade (if you choose to use us again!!) the next time you book. Odd numbers of tickets cannot be guaranteed to be together in the same row, but we will do our best. We will not be liable for any expenses. Please also note by purchasing a ticket from Double8tickets.com you are consenting to having your email address added to our mailing list. We will **NOT** share this information with any third parties. This information is for our use only. All prices are in UK Pounds Sterling and include VAT. (VAT no. 882 3824 01). **Once again Lost or stolen tickets cannot be duplicated or refunded. Please treat your tickets like cash!**

* * *

**_Privacy Policy_**

This policy governs the use by Double8Tickets.com ("we/us/our") of your (“you/your”) data which is available to us in connection with your use of our website, www.double8tickets.com (the "Website"). 

By using the Website, you are deemed to have full knowledge of and accept this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.

**1 Personal Information**

1.1 If you purchase tickets from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date) ("personal information"). We are committed to protecting your privacy, and will only use your personal information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

1.2 You are entitled to ask for a copy of your personal information at any time by contacting us at [info@double8tickets.com]. You are entitled to ask us to correct or update your personal information at any time by contacting us at the address above.

**2 Uses made of the information**

2.1 We (and our representatives) may use your personal information for the purposes of: 

2.1.1 dealing with your orders;

2.1.2 contacting you if we have trouble processing an order;

2.1.3 performing any services requested by you; and

2.1.4 record keeping.

2.2 If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s) or promotional communications, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter or promotional communications to you. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by emailing us at [info@double8tickets.com]

2.3 We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. We will disclose your Name, Billing Address and Credit Card Information to these credit card processing companies. We and these companies do not retain, share, store or use your personal information for any other purposes.

2.4 [You acknowledge that some parts of the service provided on the Website are provided by third-party service providers and not by us. You consent to us transferring your personal information to such third-party service providers for the purposes of dealing with your queries and for the purposes of record keeping.]

2.5 We may contact you from time to time to tell you about goods and services the same as or similar to those that you have enquired about. If you do not want us to contact you in this way you can "opt out" by indicating this when submitting email forms on the Website or by emailing us at any time at [info@double8tickets.com]

2.6 We and selected third parties (to whom we may pass your personal information) may wish to contact you from time to time to tell you about other matters that we believe may be of interest to you. Where you have given us your consent for us to contact you in this way, you can "opt out" by indicating this when submitting email forms on the Website or by emailing us at any time at [info@double8tickets.com]

**3 Disclosure of your information**

3.1.1 in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;

3.1.2 if our business or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets;

3.1.3 if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and any other contract entered into with us, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our customers, ourselves or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; and

3.1.4 if we determine that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of the Website.

**4 "Cookies"**

4.1 Certain parts of the Website uses "cookies" to keep track of your visit and to help you navigate between sections. A cookie is a small data file that certain websites store on your computer's hard-drive when you visit them. They can contain information such as your user ID and the pages you have visited. The only personal information a cookie contains is information you have supplied yourself.

4.2 We use cookies on the Website to enable us to deliver content that is specific to your interests and gives us an idea of which parts of the Website you are visiting. Our cookies do not read data from your computer's hard-drive or read cookies created by other websites that you have visited. This means that your visit will be tracked, but that to all intents and purposes you remain anonymous. 

4.3 You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Website. 

4.4 Please note providers of Third Party Content may also use cookies over which we have no control. 

**5 Security**

5.1 The Website has numerous security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. We cannot, however, guarantee that these measures are, or will remain, adequate. We do, however, take data security very seriously and will use all reasonable endeavours to protect the integrity of the information you provide.

**6 Changes to the privacy policy**

6.1 We reserve the right to alter this Privacy Policy at any time. Such alterations will be posted on the Website.
